A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. News summaries, 2003-2006 (Accessions 41072, 41239, 41692, 42461).
  - 2005 Feb. - 2006 Jan. (Accession 42461)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 23 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 24 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 25 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 26 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 27 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 28 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 29 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 30 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2005 Dec. 31 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 1 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 2 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 3 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 4 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 5 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 6 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 7 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 8 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 10 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 11 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 12 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 13 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - News summaries, 2006 Jan. 14 (Box 58, Folder 44)
- Series III. Photographs, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
  This series is divided into Subseries A. Images on compact discs and Subseries B. Event files.
  Corresponding compact discs and event files may exist, but in some cases material only exists in one place. It would be beneficial to the researcher to utilize both subseries. Additionally, if photographs for a certain event are not located in an event folder or on compact disc, they may be located in the miscellaneous photograph files. These files are comprised of loose photographs that were found without any identifying information. These folders are filed at the end of each year, if dates for the photographs could be determined. Those without dates or any other identifying information can be found in the miscellaneous photograph files at the end of Subseries B.
  - Subseries A. Digital images on compact discs, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
    The compact discs that compose this subseries hold digital copies of photographs. Many of these discs correspond with event files in Subseries B, but some do not. The photographs are in .jpg or .tiff formats. The discs are arranged in chronological order based on the date of the event featured. However, most discs contain photographs from several events which occurred over a period of days, weeks, or even months. For ease of research, each event is noted in the content listing, and the discs are arranged according to the earliest event date found on that particular disc. The jewel cases for each disc have a label containing its box and disc numbers. Some cases also have inserts with written descriptions of the photographs contained on that particular disc. These descriptions and event titles were created by the Press Office staff, and are not always accurate or complete. During archival processing, the photographs on each disc were examined and are described as much as possible in the content listing of this finding aid. The digital images are listed in chronological order by disc number. The discs are arranged according to the earliest date featured on each disc, and the events are listed in that order here. There are many repetitive entries because pictures for a particular event may be housed on more than one compact disc.
    - Campaigning at George Mason University, 2001 (Box 59, Disc 1)
    - George Mason University commencement (Box 59, Disc 1)
    - Transition Office, 2002 Jan. 10 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting, 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Dickenson County, 2002 Jan. 24 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Nurses' Association, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Press group with Governor, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 2)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Jan. 31 (Box 59)
    - Swearing-in of Cabinet members, 2002 Jan. 13 (Box 59, Disc 3)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting (press shots), 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 59, Disc 4)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting, 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 59, Disc 5)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting, 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Dickenson County, 2002 Jan. 24 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Fredericksburg Christian School, 2002 Jan. 31 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Snow in Grundy, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Pulaski teachers, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Blackstone, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - NOVA seniors, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Mine workers' Governor's conference, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 6)
    - Budget presentation, 2002 Jan. 22 (Box 59, Disc 7)
    - Dickenson County, 2002 Jan. 24 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Nurses' Association, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Press group, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Jan. 31 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Pulaski teachers, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Capital One, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Courtland exchange students, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Exceptional Children's Week, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Governor Dr. Kalu of Nigeria, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - Legislator's reception, 2002 Feb. 28 (Box 59, Disc 8)
    - First Lady, Cabinet and other staff photos, 2002 Jan.-Mar. (Box 59, Disc 9)
    - Pulaski teachers visit, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 10)
    - Snow, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Blackstone, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - NOVA seniors, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Mine workers' Governor's conference, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Various images, 2002 Feb. 7 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - WorldCom and Times Community newspapers, 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Race car #83, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Virginia Public Safety Foundation Valor Awards, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Press conference, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Docent appreciation dinner, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 11)
    - Copies of all previously described images on Disc 11 (Box 59, Disc 12)
    - Pulaski teachers, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Press conference, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Docent appreciation dinner, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Segway, 2002 Feb. 15 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Capital One, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Courtland exchange students, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Governor Dr. Kalu of Nigeria, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Legislators' reception, 2002 Feb. 28 (Box 59, Disc 13)
    - Leadership Blackstone, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 59, Disc 14)
    - Ministers' reception, 2002 Feb. 6 (Box 59, Disc 15)
    - Advisory Commission for Higher Education Board appointments press conference, 2002 Feb. 7 (Box 59, Disc 16)
    - Docents' reception, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 59, Disc 17)
    - Belle Wheelan, Secretary of Education photos, 2002 Feb. 26 (Box 59, Disc 18)
    - Read Across America, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 59, Disc 19)
    - Coeburn Middle School, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 59, Disc 19)
    - Various images, 2002 Mar. 4 (Box 59, Disc 19)
    - Basketball game at VCU, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Seven Hills Middle School, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - VHTP job fair, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Bath County High School, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Great Bridge High School, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Armed Services, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Press conference and meeting with Senator Howell, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - VCU Health Education Center, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Lisa Collis and Laura Bush, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 20)
    - Outstanding Faculty Awards, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Barr Labs, Blacksburg, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Governor and Tom Joyner, 2002 Mar. 14 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Various images, 2002 Mar. 18 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Berryville, VA, 2002 Mar. 19 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Cancer Society, Petersburg High School, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Consul of Japan, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 21)
    - Chaine reception, 2002 Mar. 2 (Box 59, Disc 22)
    - George Newstrom, Secretary of Transportation portraits, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 59, Disc 23)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Armed Services, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Chicken's Snack Bar, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Press conference and meeting with Senator Hall, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - VCU Health Education Center, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Barr Labs, Blacksburg, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Various images, 2002 Mar. 18-19 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Consul of Japan, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Petersburg, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 24)
    - Press conference and meeting with Senator Howell, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - VCU Health Education Center, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Barr Labs, Blacksburg, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Various images, 2002 Mar. 18-19 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Cancer Society and Petersburg High School, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Consul of Japan, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Petersburg, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 59, Disc 25)
    - Copies of all previously described images on Disc 25 (Box 59, Disc 26)
    - VCU Community Health Education Center, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 27)
    - Coordinated Economic Relief Center opening, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 59, Disc 28)
    - Danville Chamber of Commerce luncheon, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 59, Disc 28)
    - Proclamation, 2002 Apr. 2 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - VDOT Commissioner, 2002 Apr. 2 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Warren Barry, 2002 Apr. 2 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - EVMS and Hampton Roads Maritime, 2002 Apr. 3 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Child Abuse event, 2002 Apr. 4 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Stamp ceremony, 2002 Apr. 4 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Building items, 2002 Apr. 5 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Young Child proclamation, 2002 Apr. 5 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Press conference, 2002 Apr. 5 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Bill signing ceremony, 2002 Apr. 9 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Environmental initiatives, James River Park, 2002 Apr. 9 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Ceremonial bill signings, 2002 Apr. 10 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Bill signing ceremony, 2002 Apr. 11 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Apr. 16 (Box 59, Disc 29)
    - VASCIC tour, 2002 Apr. 10 (Box 59, Disc 30)
    - Virginia Living Museum, 2002 Apr. 10 (Box 59, Disc 31)
    - Roanoke tire fire, 2002 Apr.12 (Box 59, Disc 32)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Apr. 16 (Box 59, Disc 33)
    - Virginia General Assembly, 2002 Apr. 17 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Target, 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Norfolk State University, 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Bill signing, 2002 Apr. 23 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Mini press conference, 2002 Apr. 23 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Farmville and Longwood, 2002 Apr. 24 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Jimmy Hazel, 2002 Apr, 25 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Victim's Rights, 2002 Apr. 25 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Reception at Governor's Mansion, 2002 Apr. 30 (Box 59, Disc 34)
    - Target visit, 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 60, Disc 1)
    - Norfolk State University visit, 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 60, Disc 1)
    - Unknown events (could not open files), 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 60, Disc 2)
    - Cabinet members with Governor Warner, 2002 Apr. 19 (Box 60, Disc 3)
    - Basketball game at VCU, 2002 Apr. 19 (Box 60, Disc 4)
    - Earth Day, 2002 Apr. 20 (Box 60, Disc 5)
    - Prince Edward County and Longwood College, 2002 Apr. 24 (Box 60, Disc 6)
    - Moton Civil Rights Museum, 2002 Apr. 24 (Box 60, Disc 6)
    - Larry Sabato's class at University of Virginia, 2002 Apr. 24 (Box 60, Disc 6)
    - Cabinet members with Governor Warner, 2002 May 1 (Box 60, Disc 7)
    - Bike Month, 2002 May 1 (Box 60, Disc 8)
    - Bike Month, First Lady, 2002 May 1 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Various images, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Press outside of Capitol, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Jack Cooke Foundation, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - U.S.S. Cole, 2002 May 7 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Eli Lilly plant, 2002 May 8 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Virginia Public Service Awards, 2002 May 10 (Box 60, Disc 9)
    - Bike Month, First Lady, 2002 May 1 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Various images, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Press outside of Capitol, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Jack Cooke Foundation, 2002 May 2 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Ellen's birthday, 2002 May 3 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - U.S.S. Cole, 2002 May 7 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Eli Lilly plant, 2002 May 8 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Virginia Public Service Awards, 2002 May 10 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Various images, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 10)
    - Ellen's casual portraits, 2002 May 3 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - Governor's Retreat, 2002 May 5 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - FAMIS, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - Ghost Fleet, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - Bill signing and Proclamation, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - U.S. Naval Criminal Investigative Services, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - McGuire Veterans Medical Center, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - Danville, 2002 July 30 (Box 60, Disc 11)
    - Governor's Retreat, 2002 May 5 (Box 60, Disc 12)
    - U.S.S. Cole bill signing, 2002 May 7 (Box 60, Disc 13)
    - Virginia Public Service Awards, 2002 May 10 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Carver Elementary, 2002 May 14 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Photo-op conference, 2002 May 16 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Various images, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Pocahontas Parkway, 2002 May 22 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Board of Education, 2002 May 23 (Box 60, Disc 14)
    - Carver Elementary School visit, 2002 May 14 (Box 60, Disc 15)
    - FAMIS Faith-based event, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 15)
    - Carver Elementary, 2002 May 14 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Photo-op conference, 2002 May 16 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Various images, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Pocahontas Parkway, 2002 May 22 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Board of Education, 2002 May 23 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Bill signing and proclamation, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Nurse Lynda Anderson, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - U.S. Naval Criminal Investigative Services, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 16)
    - Lexington casual shots, 2002 May 15 (Box 60, Disc 17)
    - Pinner's Point, 2002 May 15 (Box 60, Disc 18)
    - VMI, 2002 May 15 (Box 60, Disc 18)
    - Holy Cow, 2002 May 15 (Box 60, Disc 18)
    - VMI Newmarket Day, 2002 May 15 (Box 60, Disc 19)
    - Ghost Fleet, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 20)
    - Ghost Fleet, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 21)
    - Firefighters' Convention, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 21)
    - FAMIS event, 2002 May 17 (Box 60, Disc 21)
    - Pocahontas Parkway (895) east-bound lane opening, 2002 May 22 (Box 60, Disc 22)
    - State Police and Volunteer Rescue Squad, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 23)
    - McGuire Veterans Memorial Hospital, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 24)
    - Rafting trip, 2002 June 6 (Box 60, Disc 24)
    - Special Olympics, 2002 June 7 (Box 60, Disc 24)
    - Nurse Lynda Anderson, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 25)
    - McGuire Veterans Memorial Hospital, 2002 May 24 (Box 60, Disc 25)
    - Smyth County, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 25)
    - Egg Factory and Koyo, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 25)
    - Smyth and Abingdon, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 25)
    - Massanutten Technical Center graduation, 2002 June 5 (Box 60, Disc 26)
    - Massanutten Technical Center graduation, 2002 June 5 (Box 60, Disc 27)
    - Park event and rafting trip, 2002 June 6 (Box 60, Disc 28)
    - Rafting, 2002 June 6 (Box 60, Disc 29)
    - Culpeper, 2002 June 6 (Box 60, Disc 29)
    - Veterans, 2002 June 7 (Box 60, Disc 29)
    - Bill signings, 2002 June 10 (Box 60, Disc 29)
    - Reception, 2002 June 24 (Box 60, Disc 29)
    - Smyth County Free Clinic, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 30)
    - Egg Factory and Koyo, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 31)
    - Smyth and Abingdon, 2002 June 11 (Box 60, Disc 31)
    - Executive Order, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 31)
    - Virginia Council of career and Technical Education, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 31)
    - Virginia Wine Advisory, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 31)
    - Executive Order, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - Virginia Council of Career and Technical Education, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - Virginia Wine Advisory, 2002 June 17 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - CF3, 2002 June 18 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - Reception One, 2002 June 18 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - McTigure, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - Executive Order signing, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 32)
    - Reception at the Mansion, 2002 June 18 (Box 60, Disc 33)
    - Reception One, 2002 June 18 (Box 60, Disc 34)
    - Boys State, 2002 June 20 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Girls State, 2002 June 20 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Reception, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Norfolk Airport, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Baptist Convention, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Tax ceremony, 2002 Nov. 27 (Box 60, Disc 35)
    - Boys State, 2002 June 20 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Girls State, 2002 June 20 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Executive Order signing, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Reception, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Norfolk Airport, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Baptist Convention, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Consolidated Bank and Trust, 2002 July 2 (Box 60, Disc 36)
    - Reception at the Mansion, 2002 June 24 (Box 60, Disc 37)
    - Asian American Mansion event, 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 38)
    - Asian American Mansion event (select photos), 2002 June 26 (Box 60, Disc 39)
    - Norfolk Airport, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 40)
    - Baptist Convention, 2002 June 27 (Box 60, Disc 40)
    - Supplier diversity announcement, 2002 July 2 (Box 60, Disc 41)
    - Consolidated Bank and Trust, 2002 July 2 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Capitol Police, 2002 July 8 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Legislative liaisons, 2002 July 8 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Governor's Fellows, 2002 July 9 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - K-12 announcement, 2002 July 11 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Keel laying, 2002 July 12 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Meterologists, 2002 July 17 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - PASS events, 2002 July 19 (Box 60, Disc 42)
    - Governor's Fellows, 2002 July 9 (Box 60, Disc 43)
    - K-12 announcement, 2002 July 11 (Box 61, Disc 1)
    - VDOT photos, 2002 July 26 (Box 61, Disc 2)
    - Danville and Roanoke, 2002 July 30-31 (Box 61, Disc 3)
    - Homeland Security, 2002 Aug. 5 (Box 61, Disc 3)
    - PASS teachers, 2002 Aug. 7 (Box 61, Disc 3)
    - Night photos of Capitol, 2002 Nov. 14 (Box 61, Disc 3)
    - Staff photos and various images, undated (Box 61, Disc 3)
    - PASS Summer Institute reception, 2002 Aug. 7 (Box 61, Disc 4)
    - PASS Roundtable, 2002 Aug. 16 (Box 61, Disc 5)
    - Petersburg, 2002 Aug. 16 (Box 61, Disc 6)
    - GAB building, 2002 Aug. 18 (Box 61, Disc 6)
    - Drought, 2002 Aug. 30 (Box 61, Disc 6)
    - Buena Vista and Covington parade, 2002 Sept. 2 (Box 61, Disc 6)
    - Staff photos and various images, undated (Box 61, Disc 6)
    - Commuter Lot, 2002 Sept. 3 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - PASS event, 2002 Sept. 4 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - National Guard event, 2002 Sept. 6 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - Virginia Corps announcement, 2002 Sept. 9 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - Cox High School, 2002 Sept. 10 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - Tax ceremony, 2002 Nov. 27 (Box 61, Disc 7)
    - Copies of all previously described images on Disc 7 (Box 61, Disc 8)
    - Buena Vista parade, 2002 Sept. 4 (Box 61, Disc 9)
    - Buena Vista parade, 2002 Sept. 4 (Box 61, Disc 10)
    - National Guard event, 2002 Sept. 6 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - NOVA, 2002 Sept. 11 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - Mariner's Museum, 2002 Sept. 17 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - Sheriff's Association conference, 2002 Sept. 17 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - State Employee Town Hall meeting, 2002 Sept. 18 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - Reston, 2002 Sept. 19 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - VCU FAMIS event, 2002 Sept. 20 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - Various images, 2002 Sept. 20 (Box 61, Disc 11)
    - Mansion reception, 2002 Sept. 9 (Box 61, Disc 12)
    - Various images, 2002 Sept. 21 (Box 61, Disc 13)
    - University of Virginia, 2002 Sept. 23 (Box 61, Disc 13)
    - Press conference, VMI and Covington, 2002 Sept. 25 (Box 61, Disc 13)
    - Bill, 2002 Sept. 26 (could not open files) (Box 61, Disc 14)
    - State Fair, 2002 Sept. 27 (could not open files) (Box 61, Disc 14)
    - Pocahontas, 2002 Oct. 4 (could not open files) (Box 61, Disc 14)
    - VMAC, 2002 Oct. 8 (could not open files) (Box 61, Disc 14)
    - Governor, 2002 Oct. 11 (could not open files) (Box 61, Disc 14)
    - Pocahontas State Park, 2002 Oct. 4 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - Conference call, 2002 Oct. 8 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - VMAC GAB, 2002 Oct. 8 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - ODU forum, 2002 Oct. 9 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - Various images, 2002 Oct. 11 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - Governor's Office photo op, 2002 Oct. 11 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - Press conference, 2002 Oct. 11 (Box 61, Disc 15)
    - Pocahontas State Park, 2002 Oct. 4 (Box 61, Disc 16)
    - VMAC GAB. 2002 Oct. 8 (Box 61, Disc 16)
    - Budget briefing, 2002 Oct. 15 (Box 61, Disc 16)
    - Coton Bridge and Mirror Ridge, 2002 Oct. 15 (Box 61, Disc 16)
    - CERT training, 2002 Oct. 19 (Box 61, Disc 17)
    - CERT training, 2002 Oct. 19 (Box 61, Disc 18)
    - Bond Campaign student lunch, 2002 Oct. 22 (Box 61, Disc 19)
    - Comcast Cable Communications Prince William County grand opening, 2002 Oct. 29 (Box 61, Disc 20)
    - Creative Playthings and American Plastics announcements, 2002 Nov. 13 (Box 61, Disc 21)
    - Payment of taxes reception and ceremony, 2002 Nov. 27 (Box 61, Disc 22)
    - Christmas decoration photos, 2002 Dec. 5 (Box 61, Disc 23)
    - VDOT visit, 2002 Dec. 6 (Box 61, Disc 24)
    - WRAP Annual Law Enforcement Award Ceremony, 2002 Dec. 12 (Box 61, Disc 25)
    - Axiom Technologies visit, 2002 Dec. 12 (Box 61, Disc 25)
    - DMV visit, 2002 Dec. 12 (Box 61, Disc 25)
    - Axiom Technologies Economic Development announcement, 2002 Dec. 12 (Box 61, Disc 26)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address (rehearsal photos), 2003 Jan. 8 (Box 61, Disc 27)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address, 2003 Jan. 8 (Box 61, Disc 28)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address, 2003 Jan. 8 (Box 61, Disc 29)
    - Portraits of Ed Mullen, Ellen Qualls, Paul Reagan and Jeff Bourne, 2003 Feb. 4 (Box 61, Disc 30)
    - Delegate Kilgore's shadow students, 2003 Feb. 10 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Delegate Amundson, 2003 Feb. 10 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Legislators' reception, 2003 Feb. 11 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Various photo ops, 2003 Feb. 11 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Conference call, 2003 Feb. 12 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Legislators' reception, 2003 Feb. 13 (Box 61, Disc 31)
    - Legislators' reception, 2003 Feb. 13 (Box 61, Disc 32)
    - Snow, YMCA, 2003 Feb. 17 (Box 61, Disc 32)
    - Basketball game, 2003 Feb. 20 (Box 61, Disc 32)
    - Photo op, 2003 Feb. 20 (Box 61, Disc 32)
    - Democratic Caucus, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 61, Disc 32)
    - Congenital Heart Defect Awareness Day, 2003 Feb. 14 (Box 61, Disc 33)
    - PASS event, 2003 Feb. 14 (Box 62, Disc 1)
    - State employees, 2003 Feb. 14 (Box 62, Disc 1)
    - Basketball game, 2003 Feb. 20 (Box 62, Disc 1)
    - Snow and Warner children outside of Mansion, 2003 Feb. 17 (Box 62, Disc 2)
    - Democratic Caucus members, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 62, Disc 3)